https://www.vasectomy-information.com/terms-conditions-privacy-policy/

Terms, Conditions & Privacy Policy
Table of Contents1 Medical Disclaimer2 Cookies Policy3 Offsite Links Disclaimer4 Advertising Policy5 Privacy Policy
Medical Disclaimer
Information contained within this site is intended for the purpose of general information ONLY, and is not medical advice. For medical advice please consult a qualified Physician. Please note that the webmaster is not a doctor, and has no medical qualifications. The webmaster is not liable for any consequences arising directly, or indirectly from information contained within the site, or on any site linked to.
Cookies Policy
This site does use cookies on some pages to test if you have previously contributed to one of the occasional surveys or quizzes. We do use Google Adsense to monetize the site, and and Google Analytics to provide web traffic statistics. Both of these services use either cookies or web beacons to track visitors. If you have any concerns about these cookies or web beacons used by Google, please refer to the Google Privacy Policies page. Also, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Offsite Links Disclaimer
Although the webmaster regularly checks any links to offsite sites and/or pages, the webmaster cannot be held responsible for the content of any external links. Nor can the webmaster be held responsible for the lack of availability of any offsite links. There are links to doctors sites on this site. The links exist for the purposes of providing information the webmaster considers useful, and are in no way an advert, or endorsement for the medical practice or service.
Advertising Policy
This site has historically been privately funded by the webmaster, without commercial sponsorship or other form of remuneration. As from January 2004, this site has been participating in, or trialing various affiliate schemes such as Google Adsense (and others) as a way of off-setting some of the costs of hosting the site. The advertisers and/or products are chosen for us by the affiliate program, but should be appropriate to the page content.
Although the webmaster regularly checks what adverts appear on the Google banners, it should be appreciated that the banners and the adverts contained within the banners are the responsibility of the banner host, and not the webmaster of this site.
Vasectomy-information.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Vasectomy-information uses and protects any information that you give while using www.vasectomy-information.com
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Vasectomy-information may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 8/15/2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
contact information including email address
demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Advertising
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Privacy policy :
This privacy policy sets out how Vasectomy Information uses and protects any information that you give while using www.vasectomy-information.com
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Vasectomy Information may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from August 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
contact information including email address
demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Advertising
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is http://www.gourmetads.com. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Opt Out
For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit https://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us.
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Name*
Email*
Website
Categories
AftercareFailureHumorMiscellaneousOverviewPicturesQ&A with Dr. KarpmanReversalRisksSex FAQsStoriesTop ArticlesUncategorized
Categories
Aftercare
Failure
Humor
Miscellaneous
Overview
Pictures
Q&A with Dr. Karpman
Reversal
Risks
Sex FAQs
Stories
Top Articles
Uncategorized
Vasectomy-Information.com contains general information about medical conditions and treatments. Although every effort is made to ensure that the material within Vasectomy-Information.com is accurate and timely, the information is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment and should not be treated as such.
Recent Posts
Must Have Products to Help You Recover After a VasectomySeptember 15, 2019
Vasectomy and prostate cancer: Facts and mythsFebruary 17, 2019
User Submitted Questions and Answers, Part 2.August 24, 2018
Recent Comments
How can you tell if a man has had a vasectomy?March 24, 2020Scrotal hematoma after vasectomyMarch 10, 2020Scrotal hematoma after vasectomyMarch 6, 2020
Pages
Miscellaneous Articles
Vasectomy Humor
Vasectomy Stories
Medical Disclaimer
Terms, Conditions & Privacy Policy
Contact
More
